tracksmith.com 2019-05-27

# Privacy Policy | Tracksmith

##### DISCLAIMER

Tracksmith collects important customer information in an effort to enhance and personalize your shopping experience. This information allows us to communicate with our customers about our products, services and promotions.

The privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) described below covers the entire Tracksmith website (“the Site,” “we,” “us,” or “our”). Phrases such as “you,” “your” and other similar expressions refer to our customers, or the specific users of this Site. By visiting and using the Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

##### COLLECTED INFORMATION

When you place an order, submit your account information or participate in Tracksmith promotions or surveys, our Site collects your personal information such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address and payment information (credit card numbers and banking accounts). Tracksmith will use your information collected online to process and fulfill your order. Additionally, your e-mail address may be collected at various points within the Site (including when you place an order with us) so that we can send you any necessary e-mail messages related to your order, such as order and shipping confirmations.

In addition, we maintain a record of your purchase history, product interests, and whatever other membership details that might enable us to improve your shopping experience. Analytics such as Site use and traffic patterns are also considered to help us improve the design of our website, the products we make and services we offer. At Tracksmith, we understand and recognize that we must maintain and use customer information responsibly.

As you navigate our site, your preferences are remembered through the temporary use of “session” cookies. Cookies enable our systems to gather information about your browser as well as monitor the navigational patterns you take while browsing the site. Site users have the option to accept or disable cookies at any time through their browsers. If you choose to disable your cookies, your user experience may be limited.

##### INFORMATION SHARING WITH OUTSIDE PARTIES

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us. However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms and Conditions.

##### AGE REQUIREMENT

Trackmith.com is intended for users who are 18 years of age and older. If you are under the age of 18, you are not permitted to submit any personal information to us.

##### SECURITY

We reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to assist us in protecting your personal information and credit card data. These safeguards help us to prevent fraud and unauthorized access as well as maintain data accuracy. In addition, we use professionally reasonable efforts to block access to your personal information from Tracksmith employees and corporate partners to ensure your personal information is always kept safe.

##### MODIFICATION OF POLICIES

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

##### QUESTIONS AND FEEDBACK

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue at info@tracksmith.com.

#### Join Our Newsletter
